# **Gabriel Aguirre**

Phone: 708.634.9295 | Email: gabriel\_aguirre@protonmail.com

**Summary:** Full-Stack Application Developer experienced in utilizing a full development stack to build, test, and deploy client-facing and internal web applications. Highly motivated team player with a strong drive to continuously learn and grow as a software developer.

#Skills

Front-End Back End Source Control Frameworks Operating Systems

Javascript ES6 PHP / Composer Git (Gitlab / Github) Laravel Unix/Linux / Terminal CSS / SASS C# / ASP.NET Subversion ASP.NET Windows / PowerShell HTML5 / XML Apache .NET Core

Webpack MySQL / SQL Server

Wordpress Vagrant

Laravel Homestead

## #Relevant Experience

### **Protective Insurance / Application Developer**

May 2019 - Present : Carmel, IN

- →Utilize C#/ASP.NET, SQL Server, and Visual Studio to update, test, and deploy ISO ratebook code in cooperation with monthly compliance sprints.
- → Perform regular updates to department-wide reporting application by utilizing SQL Server and Windows PowerShell.
- → Collaborate with business users to troubleshoot rating issues relating to internal policy administration applications.
- → Develop custom SQL Server database queries enabling the creation new department-wide reports.
- →Participate in monthly code reviews intended to improve the quality of team output.

#### University of Indianapolis / Full-Stack Web Developer

August 2016 - May 2019 : Indianapolis, IN

- →Plan, develop, and test web applications directed toward students, faculty, and staff of the university by utilizing technologies including PHP, Composer, JavaScript, Vue.js, Webpack, Bootstrap, MySQL, HTML5, CSS/SASS,
- Puppeteer, and Git on the Laravel web framework.
- →Add disability accessible functionality to new and existing university web applications using HTML5 and PHP.
- → Collaborate with university staff to perform regular maintenance of internal web applications and web forms by utilizing Wordpress, PHP, and HTML5.
- → Provide assistance and training to student web developers in web development fundamentals including HTML5, CSS/SASS, PHP, JavaScript, and MySQL.

### **Protective Insurance / Application Developer - Intern**

January 2018 - August 2018 : Carmel, IN

- → Utilize C#/ASP.NET to update ISO ratebook code in cooperation with monthly compliance sprints.
- → Perform maintenance on client-facing web applications using HTML5, CSS, and C#/ASP.NET.
- → Develop C#/ASP.NET applications to increase team productivity.

## #Education

University of Indianapolis / Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

August 2015 - May 2019 : Indianapolis, IN